[
  {
    "question": "Uranus has __________ number of moons.",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "25",
      "20"
    ],
    "correct": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "Uranus was first observed by  __________.",
    "options": [
      "William Hershel",
      "Copernicus",
      "Galileo Galilei"
    ],
    "correct": "William Hershel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not one of Uranusâ€™ moons?",
    "options": [
      "Ariel",
      "Triton",
      "Titania"
    ],
    "correct": "Triton"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the temperature on the surface of Uranus?",
    "options": [
      "-210C",
      "-219C",
      "-216C"
    ],
    "correct": "-216C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Uranus has an axial tilt of _________ degrees.",
    "options": [
      "95",
      "98",
      "96"
    ],
    "correct": "98"
  },
  {
    "question": "The number of spacecrafts that have visited Uranus is _________.",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the approximate value of polar diameter of Uranus?",
    "options": [
      "49,000-50,000 km",
      "59,000-60,000 km",
      "39,000-40,000 km"
    ],
    "correct": "49,000-50,000 km"
  },
  {
    "question": "Uranus turns on its axis once every _________ hours and ________ minutes.",
    "options": [
      "17&14",
      "13&12",
      "18&11"
    ],
    "correct": "17&14"
  },
  {
    "question": "Uranus orbits the Sun once every _______ Earth years.",
    "options": [
      "80",
      "76",
      "84"
    ],
    "correct": "84"
  },
  {
    "question": "When was Uranus discovered?",
    "options": [
      "February 16th, 1781",
      "December 18th, 1781",
      "March 13th, 1781"
    ],
    "correct": "March 13th, 1781"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mass of Uranus?",
    "options": [
      "10^26 kg",
      "10^25 kg",
      "10^24 kg"
    ],
    "correct": "10^25 kg"
  },
  {
    "question": "Uranus has _________ rings.",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "23",
      "33"
    ],
    "correct": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "Uranus is often referred to as _________.",
    "options": [
      "Gas giant",
      "Ice giant",
      "Red giant"
    ],
    "correct": "Ice giant"
  },
  {
    "question": "The distance of the orbit of Uranus is approximately _____________.",
    "options": [
      "2,870,000,000 km",
      "2,780,000,000 km",
      "2,540,000,000 km"
    ],
    "correct": "2,870,000,000 km"
  },
  {
    "question": "The name of the spacecraft sent to Uranus is __________.",
    "options": [
      "Stardust",
      "Orion",
      "Voyager"
    ],
    "correct": "Voyager"
  }
]